{
    "subject": "Harley_Cooper",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Phillip_Spaulding",
    "human_readable": "Harley Cooper is married to Phillip Spalding.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9632962346076965,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Harley Cooper and Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106670022010803,
            "question": "Are Harley Cooper and Phillip Spalding in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9051004648208618,
            "question": "To whom is Harley Cooper married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8978391289710999,
            "question": "Is Harley Cooper married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8817824125289917,
            "question": "Who is married to Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.877068817615509,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Harley Cooper and Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665292263031006,
            "question": "Who are Harley Cooper and Phillip Spalding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7683488726615906,
            "question": "Name Phillip Spalding's wife."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6315692663192749,
            "question": "Who is Harley Cooper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6280311942100525,
            "question": "What is the name of Phillip Spalding's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Harley Cooper is married to Phillip Spalding.",
            "html": "yago_25017_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Harley Cooper?",
            "html": "yago_25017_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name Phillip Spalding's wife.",
            "html": "yago_25017_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Harley Cooper and Phillip Spalding?",
            "html": "yago_25017_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25017_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text states that Harley Cooper was married to Alan-Michael Spaulding, but not Phillip Spaulding.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Harley Cooper is married to Phillip Spalding\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there are multiple mentions of Harley Cooper being married, specifically to Alan-Michael Spaulding (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25017/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25017/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt), there is no mention of her being married to Phillip Spalding."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not contain any information supporting that Harley Cooper is married to Phillip Spaulding. In fact, the documents mention that Harley Cooper was married to Alan-Michael Spaulding and that she had a relationship with Phillip Spaulding but they were not married according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}